[{"Id":3,"CardValue":1,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"},{"Id":9,"CardValue":1,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"},{"Id":18,"CardValue":1,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"},{"Id":18,"CardValue":3,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"},{"Id":4,"CardValue":1,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"},{"Id":16,"CardValue":1,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"},{"Id":5,"CardValue":2,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"},{"Id":15,"CardValue":3,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"},{"Id":9,"CardValue":1,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"},{"Id":13,"CardValue":1,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"},{"Id":12,"CardValue":1,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"},{"Id":19,"CardValue":1,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"},{"Id":1,"CardValue":2,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"},{"Id":11,"CardValue":2,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"},{"Id":13,"CardValue":3,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"},{"Id":6,"CardValue":1,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"},{"Id":16,"CardValue":1,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"},{"Id":15,"CardValue":2,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"},{"Id":20,"CardValue":3,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"},{"Id":9,"CardValue":1,"Question":"QUESTION","Answers":["CORRECT","FAIL","FAIL","FAIL"],"CorrectAnswer":"CORRECT"}]